videouniversity.com 2013-05-23

# VideoUniversity Privacy Policy « VideoUniversity

Welcome to VideoUniversity.com’s website. We appreciate your interest. When you visit and navigate our site and when you communicate with us via our site, we will not collect personal information about you unless you provide us that information voluntarily.

(In some cases, and in all cases where required by law or regulation, you will be able to update the information that you provide to us either by sending us an email or, where you have established personal profiles with us, by updating your profile online. Please refer to the specific pages where data is collected for more information.) VideoUniversity.com will not sell, license, transmit or disclose this information outside of VideoUniversity.com and its affiliated companies unless (a) expressly authorized by you, (b) necessary to enable VideoUniversity.com contractors or agents to perform certain functions for us, or (c) required or permitted by law. In all cases, we will disclose the information consistent with applicable laws and regulations and we will require the recipient to protect the information and use it only for the purpose it was provided.

By personal information, we mean data that is unique to an individual, such as a name, address, email address, or telephone number. From time to time, we may request personal information from you in order to deliver requested materials to you, respond to your questions, or deliver a product or service.

## Your email

We welcome your comments or questions about VideoUniversity and have provided email links for that purpose. We will share your comments and questions with our customer service representatives and those employees most capable of addressing your questions and concerns.

Please note that your email, like most, if not all, non-encrypted Internet email communications, may be accessed and viewed by other Internet users, without your knowledge and permission, while in transit to us. For that reason, to protect your privacy, please do not use email to communicate information to us that you consider confidential. If you wish, you may contact us instead via non-cellular telephone at the numbers provided at various locations on our sites.

## Other Information; “Cookies” and “Tags”

You should also be aware that when you visit our websites, we collect certain information that does not identify you personally, but provides us with “usage data,” such as the number of visitors we receive or what pages are visited most often. This data helps us to analyze and improve the usefulness of the information we provide at this website.

Like most commercial website owners, we may use what is known as “cookie” technology. A “cookie” is an element of data that a website can send to your browser when you link to that website. It is not a computer program and has no ability to read data residing on your computer or instruct it to perform any step or function. By assigning a unique data element to each visitor, the website is able to recognize repeat users, track usage patterns and better serve you when you return to that site. The cookie does not extract other personal information about you, such as your name, address, or email.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. One such third party advertising company is Google. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to this and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html "Google Ad Privacy Policy").

Cookies can be very helpful to you if you are a member of the VideoUniversity.com forums, but you can still use the forums without enabling cookies.

## Linking to Other Sites

From time to time, VideoUniversity.com websites may provide links to other websites, not owned or controlled by VideoUniversity.com, that we think might be useful or of interest to you. We cannot, however, be responsible for the privacy practices used by other website owners or the content or accuracy of those other websites. Links to various non-VideoUniversity.com websites do not constitute or imply endorsement by VideoUniversity.com of these websites, any products or services described on these sites, or of any other material contained in them.

## Security

VideoUniversity.com has adopted and adheres to stringent security standards designed to protect non-public personal information at VideoUniversity.com against accidental or unauthorized access or disclosure. Among the safeguards that VideoUniversity.com has developed for this site are administrative, physical and technical barriers that together form a protective firewall around the information stored at this site. We periodically subject our site to simulated intrusion tests and have developed comprehensive disaster recovery plans. All financial transactions such as purchasing a product or service from VideoUniversity.com has the strongest security measures so that your transactions are fully protected.

## Changes to This Statement

VideoUniversity.com may change this Statement from time to time. We encourage you to periodically reread this Policy to see if there have been any changes that may affect you. This Statement is not intended to and does not create any contractual or other legal rights in or on behalf of any party.

No comments yet.

  *[RSS]: Really Simple Syndication
